Through dark slats, a blue light glows.
A slender, large-headed figure of blue particles.
A tiny machine splits a sphere.
A ship chips at an asteroid.
Blinding light channels into a satellite. A Sophon stands proudly.
The Sophon facepalms in the smoke.
They touch a glowing fault line.
A hologram moon shatters. They flinch, then stand shoulder-to-shoulder, gazing at a glowing spire.
One gives a thumbs up.
The room falls away. The spire is the core of a colossal station. Massive metallic ribs spiral upward around a blinding blue pillar of energy.
They stand at the station's base.
The colossal station turns slowly in the dark void. Everything fades to black.